// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which tag is the root element of an HTML document?",
    answer: "html",
    options: [
      "DOCTYPE html",
      "body",
      "html",
      "root"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which type of variable keeps a constant value once it is assigned?",
    answer: "final",
    options: [
      "non-static",
      "private",
      "final",
      "static"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is used to capture data from the physical world in IoT devices?",
    answer: "sensors",
    options: [
      "sensors",
      "microcontrollers",
      "actuators",
      "microprocessors"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " What type of computing technology refers to services and applications that typically run on a distributed network through virtualized resources?",
    answer: "cloud computing",
    options: [
      "distributed computing",
      "cloud computing",
      "soft computing",
      "parallel computing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Choose the correct components of data science.",
    answer: "all of the above",
    options: [
      "domain expertise",
      "data engineering",
      "advanced computing",
      "all of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The runtime system starts your program by calling which function first?",
    answer: "main",
    options: [
      "hello",
      "iterative",
      "print",
      "main"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which statement accurately describes how items are added to and removed from a stack?",
    answer: "a stacks adds items to the top and removes items from the top.",
    options: [
      "a stacks adds items to one side and removes items from the other side.",
      "a stacks adds items to the top and removes items from the top.",
      "a stacks adds items to the top and removes items from anywhere in the stack.",
      "a stacks adds items to either end and removes items from either end."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When using position: fixed, what will the element always be positioned relative to?",
    answer: "the viewport",
    options: [
      "the wrapper element",
      "the parent element",
      "the viewport",
      "the closest element with position: relative"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which style places an element at a fixed location within its container?",
    answer: "position: absolute",
    options: [
      "position: absolute",
      "display: flex",
      "float: left",
      "display: block"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Pick the incorrect statement about inline functions in C++?",
    answer: "they are generally very large and complicated function",
    options: [
      "saves overhead of a return call from a function",
      "they are generally very large and complicated function",
      "these functions are inserted/substituted at the point of call",
      "they reduce function call overheads"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];